ascendgence.com 2012-01-24

# Ascendgence Privacy, Information and Security Policy - Ascendgence

Ascendgence guarantees that no personal information will be released to an individual, corporation or any other business entity without written authorization from the client specifying what information may be released and to whom it may be released.

## Ascendgence Collection of Information

There are various methods by which we collect client or user information. This information is all protected by this Ascendgence privacy policy and will not be released to any third party without consent from the client.  
When you contract for services from Ascendgence, we require basic personal or company information which will include but will not be limited to your name, company, address, email address, phone and fax.  
We retain information which may be personal and given voluntarily at other times, including but not limited to when you provide opinions pertaining to complaints, appreciation and comments on the service/product being provided by Ascendgence. All of these types of information are held in confidence unless release is authorized by client.

## Non-Disclosure of Personal or Company Information

We will not reveal your Personal or Company Information to unaffiliated third parties without your consent. If we seek your consent to disclose your Information to a third party, we will do so unambiguously, explaining precisely what information we seek to disclose and to who. As a matter of company philosophy and policy, we would rarely have cause to seek this authorization.  
Ascendgence will release Personal or Company information if Ascendgence will be legally bound to reveal information, including Personal or Company Information, to the extent it reasonably believes it is required to do so by law. If Ascendgence receives legal process calling for the disclosure of any of its clients Personal or Company Information we will, if permitted by law, attempt to notify the client via e-mail or telephone within a reasonable amount of time before we respond to the request.

## Security

We employ reasonable and current security methods to prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure correct use of information.  
Your personal or Company data will be stored within a database that is located behind a firewall for added security. The server housing the database is physically protected at a secure, third party site and is monitored by security personnel twenty-four hours a day. Only authorized personnel can access the data center and the particular server housing the database.  
No data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be secure. As a result, while we try to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.  
We do not encrypt your normal web sessions with the Service using SSL. Any transmission to the Ascendgence website or service of credit card information uses SSL encryption.  
Ascendgence uses industry standard virus protection on all of our commuter systems.

## Ascendgence Privacy Policy Change

Ascendgence may change its privacy policy but all changes made regarding disclosure of Personal or Company Information to third parties will be made after notification through electronic means prior to the date the modified policy takes effect. Any new policy will have effect only, to information previously gathered without your express consent. 

Ascendgence LLC – January 2011
